12 个 月 前
-走  -快 快 快
- Let's go. - Move, move, move, move!
武装警察
Armed police!
武装警察 趴下
Armed policel Get down!
肖恩·华莱士死了
Sean Wallace is dead.
我重复 肖恩·华莱士死了
I repeat, Sean Wallace.
这里 帮帮我
Here, help me.
离床
Clear.
把他带上车
Get him in the van!
离床
Clear.
他死了吗
Is he dead?
他还在呼吸 开车
He's breathing. Drive.
快
Hurry.
左转
Take the left.
除颤仪
Defibrillator.
充电 离床 电击
Charging. Clear. Shock.
好了 我们找到他了 情况不好
Okay, we have him. He's in a bad way...
准备缝合 缝合开始
Sutures in place. Entering now.
我在哪
Where am I?
我们需要你的配合
We would like your cooperation
涉及到被你称之为投资者的集团
concerning a group you call the Investors.
会有你好处的
You would be rewarded.
你为他们工作吗
You work for them?
正相反
The opposite.
你不是警察吧
You're not the police.
某种形式上算是
A version of it.
那就给我滚开
Well, then...fuck off.
去你妈的
Fuck you!
起来
Get up!
现 在
告诉我昨晚在鱼市发生了什么
Tell me about last night. The fish market.
一个枪手 男性 30岁左右
One shooter. Male. Thirties.
也许是职业杀手
Maybe professional?
不太像
Not very.
你看到他的脸了吗
You saw his face, yes?
没有
No?
-也许你  -是比利·华莱士
- Perhaps you... - It was Billy Wallace.
肖恩的哥哥
Sean's brother.
Sean's brother?
-你能解释一下吗  -我特么不知道
- Can you explain? - I don't fucking know.
你让我找个枪手 我找了
You asked me to find a shooter, and I did.
你之后要去哪
Where did you go after? Hm?
艾略特帮忙出手杀比利·华莱士之后他要去哪
Where does Elliot go after he helps kill Billy Wallace?
吃早餐
Breakfast.
早餐哈
- Breakfast. - Hm.
吐司 花草茶
You know, toast. Some herbal tea.
我明白
I understand.
你就像是个秘密特工一样
You're like a secret fucking agent.
谁特么知道你会去哪 你到底看到了什么
Who knows where you go...what you really see?
如果你再看到华莱士家人 就告诉我
You see any more Wallaces out there...you let me know.
明白吗 否则我会觉得你不喜欢我
Hm? Or I'll think you don't like me.
金融家亚历克斯·杜马尼死亡
警方调查结果明显自杀
比利
Billy.
吃药
Take these.
谢谢
Thanks.
昨晚的枪手是什么人
Who were those shooters last night?
你碰巧遇上了而已吧
You walked into something.
可不是 我说过谢谢了吗
Yeah, no shit. Have I said thanks?
我不能失去你们俩比利
I'm not losing you both, Billy.
妈跟我说了
- Yeah, Mum told me. - Yeah...
你在跟踪我吗
Were you following me?
没有 我在跟踪别人 你就是走运
No. Following someone else. You were just lucky.
鱼市的那个家伙 杀手 是你吗
The guy at the fish market, the hit, that was you?
到底怎么回事 肖恩
What the fuck is going on, Sean?
在车里 你说跟你一起的一个人失踪了
In the car, you said one of the men you came with went missing.
妈手下的
One of Mum's men.
是 达拉
Yeah. Darragh.
他去找卢安了 我不
He went to Luan. I don't...
我得跟妈谈谈
I need to speak to Mum.
她有麻烦了吗
She in trouble?
她肯定会问问题
She'll have some questions.
你的衣服在那
Your clothes are there.
达拉和基利安失踪 卢安没动静
Darragh and Killian are still missing. Luan's gone silent.
-科巴肯定说动他们了  -比利呢
- Koba's got to someone. - And Billy?
-我们说好的 玛丽安  -伦尼就回来了
- We had a deal, Marian. - Lennie's on his way back.
-你说你可以保护我们  -我们这就走了
- You said you could protect us. - We're leaving.
或者你可以坐自己的游艇逃跑
Or you can just run off to your yacht
等着他们抓到你
and wait for them to track you down.
别忘了把钱留下
Just make sure you leave money.
如果我想 很久以前我就做了
If I wanted, I would have done it a long time ago.
芬恩的钱肯定会引人注意 你知道的
Finn's money will always attract attention. You know this.
我知道战争是什么样 我经历过
I know what war is, Marian. I lived through one.
如果我们现在藏起来 下次一定要狠狠还击 我们不能退缩
If we hide now, we hit them hard next. We don't back down.
你特么以为自己跟谁说话呢
Who the fuck do you think you're talking to?
我救了你 作为交换你答应过给我
I saved your life, and in exchange we promised each other
权力和影响力
power and strength.
你不记得答应过我了吗
Do you remember agreeing to that?
她不能过跟我一样的生活
She won't have the life I had.
罗莎 罗莎
Roze. Roze. Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
我们为孩子计划了一切
We all have plans for them.
可等他们长大之后 就只会报答你一拳
Then they grow up, punch you in the face.
伦尼回来了 拿上东西
Lennie's back. Get your things.
有比利的消息吗
Anything from Billy?
我会再去仔细找一定能找到 我发誓
I'll track every step he took. I'll find him, I swear.
比利吗
Billy?
不是 妈 是我
No, Mum. It's me.
你是谁
Who is this?
肖恩 妈
It's Sean, Mum.
我是肖恩
It's Sean.
现在我没法解释 但你得听我说
I can't explain now. You need to listen to me.
比利很安全
Billy's safe.
你需要离开那
And you need to get out of there.
科巴派人去杀你了
Koba's coming for you.
妈 妈
Mum? Mum?
妈 你还在吗 说话啊 妈
Mum, are you there? Speak to me, Mum.
妈 你能听见吗 你现在有危险
Mum, can you hear me? You're in danger!
妈 你现在有危险
Mum, you're in danger!
罗莎
Roze!
罗莎在楼上 我得去抱她
Roze's upstairs! I have to get her!
快点 起来 行了 起来
Come on, quick. That's it. Get up, that's it!
好了 待在这 留在这 找掩护
That's it, stay here. Stay here. Stay there. Stay down.
-不  -罗莎
- No! - Roze.
罗莎 罗莎 罗莎
Roze. Roze. Roze.
罗莎
Roze!
你找到她了吗
Did you find her yet?
还没 正在找
Not yet, still looking.
罗莎
Roze, shh, shh.
快 佛里安娜 起来 快
Come on. Floriana, get up. Get up, come on.
-我们得离开这  -罗莎
- We've got to get out of here. - Oh, Roze.
快 快
Come on. Come on.
-把她给我  -给
- Give her to me. - Here.
伦尼 伦尼
Lennie? Lennie?
不 不 快跑 我掩护
No, no. Run! I've got this.
-快快  -跑
- Go! Go! - Run.
去树林里 后面
To the woods, out back.
草泥马 玛丽安 去你妈的
Fuck you, Marian. Fuck you.
找到她们了吗
Are they with you yet?
没有
Not yet.
我还在找
I'm looking.
等你找到他们打给我
Call me when you have them.
我看见他们了
I see them.
3 个 月 前
警卫
Guard!
你想让我在英国法庭上作证
You would like me to testify before a British court...
供出有关投资者的一切
on everything I know about the Investors.
你会受到本州的全面保护
You would have the full protection of the state.
你提供的证据也将是匿名的
Your evidence would be anonymous.
就像是幽灵一样
You'd be a ghost.
之后会有个全新的生活
Afterwards, a new life.
当然会有限制条件
With certain restrictions.
你认为那样就可以将投资者从伦敦铲除
And you think that will remove the Investors from London?
照你提供的情况
With what's in your head,
我们会对他们进行前所未有的大力打击
we'll hit them harder than they've ever been hit.
那你就太特么蠢了
Well, you're fucking stupid.
如果你想铲除他们 你需要接手他们控制的一切
If you want them gone, you have to take what they control.
街头 帮派 塔楼
Street by street. Gang by gang. Tower by tower.
你需要把他们连根拔起
You'd have to destroy them from the ground up.
你需要 让王者回归
You need...a returning king.
你炸了你父亲的王国 现在你想成为他
You blew up your father's city. Now you want to be him.
你没自己想的那么聪明
You're not as clever as you think you are.
想让肖恩·华莱士死的人
The people who wanted Sean Wallace dead...
你才刚刚触及到表面
you've only just brushed up against them.
我已经参与了多年
I've been on this for years.
城市已经发生了变化 投资者现在有新玩家了
The city's changed. The Investors have a new player.
他们不会想到我能回去 就像你说的 我就像个幽灵
They won't see me coming. Like you said, I'm a ghost.
我需要同一个世界的人 一个黑帮分子
I'll need people from my world. A gang.
她在哪
Where is she?
不可能
Impossible.
她对我来说有很大的价值 是可以交易的资源
She's of high value to me. A trading asset.
卖给她的敌人吗
To sell to her enemies?
政治
Politics.
你还不是我们要的全局
You're not the whole picture here.
那就谈不成了
Then no deal.
你信任她
You trust her?
我说了我需要她
I said I need her.
她的军事训练
Her military training.
她的手下
Her people.
来吧
Come.
跟着我
Follow me.
跟娜扎走 娜扎
Go with Naza. Naza...
我记不太清楚了
I don't have clear memories.
我记得拉莱 还有她的手下
I remember Lale, her people,
他们把我从酒店里弄了出去
they pulled me out of that hotel.
然后呢
Then what?
他们找人给我治了伤
They found someone to put me back together.
都是拉莱的人帮的忙吗
Lale's people did all that?
嗯
Yeah.
为什么
Why?
我也帮过他们啊 不是吗
I helped them, didn't I?
他们就是还个人情
They repay their debts.
听我说 科巴现在已经卡住他喉咙了
Listen to me. Koba's got them by the neck now.
他从利润里拿掉了很大一部分
He takes a hefty cut of their profits,
在他们包装产品时 他像鹰一样盯着
and whilst they package his product, he watches like a hawk.
我得尽快送你到个安全的地方 妈
I need to get you somewhere safer soon, Mum.
你在这多久了
How long have you been here?
3个月
3 months.
只能这样
It had to be this way.
就拿起电话
All you had to do was pick up the phone
告诉我们你还活着有那么难吗
and tell us you were still breathing.
-会有风险的  -我都不知道你还活着
- It would have been a risk. - I didn't even know you were alive.
没有他拖后腿的家庭会更容易 他说的没错
It was easier without his fuck-up family. He's got a point.
你到底在做什么
What have you been doing exactly?
塔楼 钱 帮派
The towers. The money. The gangs.
-我都要拿回来  -你脑子没坏掉吧
- I'm taking it all back. - Did they fix your head right?
-我认真的  -就带着这些恐怖分子吗
- I mean it. - With a bunch of terrorists?
-搞笑呢吧  -还有其他人
- Seriously? - Others will join.
等他们意识到科巴不是未来 我才是的时候
Once they realize Koba's not the future, I am.
但这事你不能插手 科巴在你的组织里面有内线
But you need to step back. Koba's got inside your networks.
你不知道该信任谁
You don't know who to trust.
如果我要给父亲的女友提供庇护
And if I'm to give shelter to my father's girlfriend,
我需要知道你欠她什么
I need to know what you owe her.
她救过我一命
She saved my life.
那她就是家人了
Then she's family.
来 用这个吧
Here. Use this instead.
他想称王 是不是
He wants to be king, doesn't he?
搞了一群叛军过来
He's got his little rebel army here.
那你怎么办
Where does that leave you?
试着睡会吧
Try and get some sleep.
别假装你看不出来
Don't pretend this isn't happening.
他会最后的目标是你 要走所有的钱
He'll come to you, ask for all the money,
到时就什么都没有了
and that's when it's over.
-不可能  -对 因为我是不会答应的
- That's not gonna happen. - No. Because I won't say yes.
我是肖恩
I'm Sean.
-你还好吗  -经历过比这糟糕的
- Is everything all right here? - I've known worse.
那是
I bet.
给我抱抱行吗
May I?
你好啊
Hello.
我以为能看到爸的眼神呢
I was expecting to see Dad looking back at me.
但是没有 没长华莱士家人的眼睛
But no. Not the Wallace eyes.
幸好呢
Lucky break.
罗莎
Roze. Shh, shh, shh.
怎么回事
What's going on?
科巴的人抓走了罗让
Koba's men took Rojan.
他们想要什么
What do they want?
罗让偷偷卖货 科巴一定是发现了
Rojan was selling on the side. Koba must have found out.
我们还有什么选择 科巴分走了一大块利润
What choice do we have? Koba takes most of our profits.
我们都没有足够钱寄回家
There's not enough to send home.
我们说过要小心的
We agreed to be careful.
小心
Careful?
如果科巴发现玛丽安·华莱士在这呢
What if Koba found Marian Wallace here?
我们只跟肖恩·华莱士合作
Our deal was with Sean Wallace.
-而不是他的家人  -我会处理
- Not his family. - I'll handle it.
自从你回来 大家就在说
People have been talking since you came back.
她还知道自己是谁吗
Does she still know who she is?
你母亲在这会给我们惹来麻烦
This is a problem for us, your mother being here.
我们会另找个地方给他们
We'll find somewhere for my family.
我的人接受不了继续这样
My people can't continue like this.
等时机一到我们就会对付科巴
We'll hit Koba when the time's right.
他们不是没有耐心
Patience is not the problem.
只是需要看到你能履行承诺
They need faith that you can deliver what you promised.
你现在压力很大 我懂
You're under pressure. I understand.
他们需要对你有信心
They need faith in you.
你为什么要回来救我
Why did you come back for me?
你知道的太多 我是救自己
You know too much. I was protecting myself.
那我是该很高兴
That's good to know.
你要真想兑现自己的承诺
If you want what you claim, you must be prepared
就必须做好不惧一切排除万难的准备
to do everything without fear, without care.
这是你的职责
This is what it asks of you.
格鲁吉亚人来了
The Georgians are coming.
他们抓了罗让
They've got Rojan.
该死
Oh, shit.
你们需要躲起来 快 科巴的人来了
You need to hide. Come on. Koba's men are here.
-马上  -出什么事了
- Quick. - What's going on?
-快 快点  -走
- Quick. Come on, come on. - Mum, go.
走走走 快走
Go, go, go, go, go.
抓紧时间
Quick.
梅尔万
Merwan...
-还好吗  -还好
- How's life? - Good.
老婆开心 一切就开心了 对吧
Happy wife, happy life, eh?
我有个问题
- I have a question. - Mm.
你对产品的质量满意吗
Are you happy with the quality of the product?
-客人们都满意吗  -对
- Are the customers happy? - Yes.
关于你员工的工作时长
The hours your employees are required to work,
我们谈过了 对吧
we negotiated that, yes?
我们要求每天工作10小时 可以接受吗
We asked for 10 hours a day. That is acceptable?
待在这
Stay here.
工时费有问题吗 没有吧
The hourly rate, is that a problem? No?
没有
No.
那咱们之间就没啥大矛盾了 对吧
So there's no general big problem between us, correct?
对
- No. - No.
哦 亲爱的 不
Oh, my love. No, no!
那么 这个小偷
So...this thief...
就只是个小麻烦了
he's a small problem, nothing more.
为什么
Why?
你不是因为心怀不满 才让他去偷窃的 对吧
You never asked him to steal because you are not unhappy, huh?
他是你兄弟吧 我是说亲兄弟
He's your brother, yes? I mean, real brother?
同一个妈生的
- The same mother?
你们的人都以兄弟姐妹相称
You all call each other brother, sister.
-就是核实下  -他是我兄弟
- I'm just checking. - He's my brother.
-嘿  -别
- Hey... - No.
我觉得你兄弟骗了我
I think your brother is lying to me.
别
No.
怎么 你想跟他交换位置吗
Oh! You want to take his place.
不 不要
No. No, no...
那好吧
Okay!
把你手给我
Give your hand.
不不不
No. No, no.
别这样 塔玛兹 不要
No, Tamaz. No.
不
No!
告诉你的工人 工作时长现在是12个小时了
Please tell your workers, the shift is now 12 hours.
我们多送一些 你们多打包一些
We deliver more, you package more.
双赢
Win, win.
咱们走吧
Let's go.
库尔德人那边进行得如何了
How's it progressing with the Kurds?
科巴跟我们的矛盾加剧了
Koba's becoming a bigger problem for us.
我已经控制住了
I've got it under control.
你爸的女友跟你妈联手了
And your father's girlfriend working with your mother?
我说了我在处理
I said I'm handling it.
复仇的那扇窗要关上了 肖恩
The window to retaliate is closing, Sean.
抱歉
Sorry.
你想让我
Do you want me to...?
你想让她也变成我们吗
Do you want her to be like us?
你觉得我不应该来这
You think I shouldn't be here?
你不能由着性子行事
You can do what you like.
我父亲好赌 他帮黑手党押注
My father was a gambler. He ran bets for the mafia.
他也不想 可他没拒绝的权利
He didn't want to, but you don't say no.
但有天他还是拒绝了
Then he said no.
在我家厨房被他们爆头
They shot him in the head in our kitchen.
他们还打死了我的小弟
My little brother too.
怕他长大寻仇
So he wouldn't grow up and take vengeance.
我早看清了这个世界的模样
I know what this world is.
罗莎
Roze.
你有多了解我母亲
How well do you know my mother?
或许我了解你不知道的那一面
Maybe I know some things you don't.
那你肯定知道 她最后会卖了你
Then you'll know that she'll screw you over in the end.
拉莱 长老们要召集会议了
Lale, the elders have called a meeting.
我们得谈谈华莱士的事
We need to discuss the Wallaces.
肖恩
Sean.
你先请
After you.
听说你们不开心 我能如何效劳
I'm told you're unhappy. How can I make you happy?
你母亲的行动 卢安 给我们帮了倒忙
The actions of your mother, Luan, this does not help us.
科巴觉察出叛乱的气息 把我们逼得更紧了
Koba smells rebellion, so he pushes us.
我们利润太薄 连寄回家的钱都没有
There is too little profit to send home,
我们跟城里的其他帮派不同
We're not the same as others in this city, yeah?
他们夺权是为了自己
Those who want power for its own sake.
我们则是在为祖国人民的自由而战
My people want freedom in our homelands.
如果这里的生意做不下去 像现在这样
If our business here fails, as it fails now,
我们会去别的城市
for us there are other cities,
找别的营生继续斗争
other ways to continue the struggle.
你们的生意不会做不下去
Your business won't fail.
等科巴倒台 你们会在这个城市有一席之地
When Koba's gone, you'll have a place in this city.
我向你们保证
I promised you that.
你行动太慢了
Too slow.
我曾说过 与科巴同谋就是于我为敌
I said I'd hit anyone who sides with Koba.
现在看来这句话要升级了
That's not enough now. It's time to escalate.
我们也很想相信你
We'd like to share your confidence.
我们需要彼此
Yeah, we need each other.
但你更需要我们 没了我们 你就是光杆司令
But you need us more. Without us, you're alone.
我会给你们寄回家的钱
I'll give you money to send home.
也会给你们寄回家的武器
I'll give you weapons for the fight ahead.
你真有权承诺给我们这些吗
These things are yours to give?
你妈有她自己的打算 对吗
Your mother has her own ambitions, no?
我已经说过了 我说到做到
Like I said, you have my word.
该让我们看到好处了
Then let us see.
我记得这个
I remember this.
街头混混 对吗
Street grunt, isn't it?
手举起来
Hands up.
坐前排 快
Front seat. Come on.
我以为你会头一个来杀我
Thought I'd be higher up your kill list.
巧了 有人告诉我你不能碰
Funny. I was told you were off limits.
约瑟夫·辛格 他特别交代过
Joseph Singer. He was very insistent.
原来你我暂时在同一战线上
Turns out you and I are on the same side. For now.
我根本不在乎你 也不在乎什么辛格
I do not give a fuck about you or Singer.
但科巴在乎 尤其你在对他的新朋友痛下杀手
But Koba would. Especially as you've been killing his new friends.
看到这个了吗
See this here?
医生说再深一根头发丝的距离 我就
The surgeon said a hair either way and, pff...
奇迹啊 真的
Miracle, really.
然后我想 他是故意的吧
Then I thought, did he mean to do it?
太符合艾略特的风格了 他不想出卖灵魂
That's very Elliot. Anything for a clean conscience.
不客气
Say thank you.
你太会骗人了
You're such a good liar.
骗的自己都信了
You even fall for your own bullshit.
我申请了最难办的案子 芬恩的案底千头万绪
I asked for the worst case, you know. Finn's file was huge.
洗钱 勒索 共谋
Money laundering, extortion, conspiracy,
故意伤害 虐杀 绑架 贩运
ABH, GBH, murder, kidnap, trafficking.
而你的案底 却空无一物
Yours...was empty.
什么都没有 也没人在乎
Nothing. No one cares.
你无关紧要
You're an irrelevance.
你不是你爸爸
You're not your dad
你也做不来这些苟且
and you don't know how to do any of this.
你说完了吗
You finished?
辛格说你又回来了 但你想退出
Singer said you're back in, but you want out.
最好下定决心 你我都知道你来此的真正目的
Make your mind up We both know why you're really here.
我们俩的目标一致
You and I want the same thing.
把投资人赶出这座城
To rid this city of the Investors.
所以要么帮我 要么滚蛋
So either help me or fuck off.
开枪吧
Go on, then.
你没说错
You're right
何必呢 你我共寄一个屋檐下
Don't have to. You're all hiding under one roof.
你只要科巴拉莱的地址给我
Could just give Koba Lale's address,
华莱士一家就齐齐整整了 对吧
and that's all the Wallaces in one, right?
我们不在同一战线
We're not on the same side.
肖恩呢
Where's Sean?
他说你和你的人救了他的命
He says you and your people saved his life.
你从中能得到什么呢拉莱
What's in this for you, Lale, hm?
看到我回来 你心里滋味一定不好受
Must have killed you to see me walking back in here.
你觉得这下他可以乖乖听命于你了 对吗
Thought you had him wrapped around your little finger, didn't you?
你内心一定很难接受吧
This is hard for you, isn't it?
什么
What is?
他已经不再惧怕你了
He's not scared of you anymore.
他在屋顶上等你
He's waiting for you on the roof.
肖恩 怎么了
Sean, what's going on?
你他妈刚才去哪儿了
Where the fuck have you been?
关于我的经历 我没说实话
I lied about what happened to me.
-你现在要认真听我说  -不
- I want you to listen closely. - No.
你听我说 我受够了
You listen to me. I've had enough.
你再敢骗我一次 我们一刀两断
One more lie out of your mouth and we're done.
我中枪后 我没跟拉莱的人在一起
After I was shot, I wasn't with Lale's people
我被别人带走了
I was taken by someone else.
被关了起来 拉莱也是
I was a captive. Lale too.
投资人还有其他敌人
The Investors have other enemies.
有些人是政府内部人士
Some of them inside our government.
他们人不多 而且行踪诡秘
They're secretive and they're few,
他们想让投资人出局
and they want the Investors out.
与我的目标一致
They and I want the same thing.
你到底想要什么
What are you after?
我想告诉你全部真相 我们之间重新开始
I want you to know everything. I want a clean slate between us.
不
No.
我问你想要什么
What do you want?
我想让你把爸的钱给我
I want you to give me Dad's money.
我想要你军火商的人脉
And I want your arms contacts.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
你跟佛里安娜 是怎么谈拢的
You and Floriana, how does it work?
别想了
Forget it.
那些账户在她控制之下 你父亲都安排好了
She controls the accounts. Your father saw to that.
所以是怎么操作的 是你求着她吗
So how does it work, then? Do you beg?
她在我孤立无援的时候帮了我
She helped me when there was nobody else around for me.
-我不能夺走她的一切  -老了老了 突然生出同情心了
- I can't just take everything from her. - Grown sentimental in your old age.
-滚  -原来你不相信我
Fuck off. I'm the one you don't trust!
-当然不相信你 肖恩  -对不起
- Bloody right I don't trust you, Sean. - I'm sorry.
不 你不是真心的 你这么说是因为你对我有事相求
No, you're not. You're only sorry you're having to beg for what's mine.
-我本该告诉你我还活着  -你当然应该
- I should have told you I was alive. - Yes, you should have!
-我以为你死了  -对不起
- I thought you were dead. - I'm sorry.
-对不起  -你让我伤心欲绝
- I'm sorry. - You crucified me!
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起
Sorry.
曾有那么多日日夜夜 月复一月
There were days and weeks and months,
我脑中空无一物 忘了自己是谁
inside what was left of my head, when I forgot who I was.
现在我知道了
But I know now.
我是华莱士
I'm a Wallace.
我生是华莱士的人 死是华莱士的鬼
I'm a fucking Wallace, all or nothing.
我会保护我们 夺回我们的荣耀
And I'm gonna protect us and get what we deserve.
别着急 你很快就会收到钱了
Be patient You'll receive the money soon, okay?
什么时候 我也不知道
When? When? I don't know when.
你的人需要帮助
Your people need help.
寄希望于肖恩·华莱士是个错误
If you're looking to Sean Wallace, it would be a mistake.
我可以给你们提供更好的
I can offer you something better.
我有渠道
I have the means.
有人脉
And the connections.
想让我继续说下去吗
Shall I continue?
但有一个条件
There would be a condition.
干嘛
What?
我能告诉你一个秘密吗
Can I tell you a secret?
老爸曾有点害怕你
Dad was scared of you.
他知道你比他聪明
He knew you were smarter than him.
你是故意离开家的 对吗
You got lost on purpose, didn't you?
让他再也不能卷你进入家族生意
So he'd never want you involved,
你能看清人的本质
You see people for what they are.
也能识破所有花招
You don't miss a trick, do you?
我需要你留下来保护我
I need you here, watching my back.
你愿意吗 比利
Will you do that, Billy?
愿意
Yeah, I will.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢了
跟我来
Come with me.
我跟拉莱和梅尔万谈过了
I've spoken with Lale and Merwan.
从今往后 我负责支持他们的生意
From now on, I will support their business.
是真的吗
Is this true?
耍阴招你可没闲着
Well, you're a busy devil.
你也会这么对我的
You would have done this to me.
所以你现在想让我做什么
So what would you like me to do now?
离开
Leave.
你本来能得到想要的一切
You could have had what you wanted.
但你太害怕了
But you're afraid to do it.
我会兑现承诺的
You'll have what I promised.
求你
♪ Please ♪
睁开双眼
♪ Open your eye ♪
试着
♪ Try ♪
看一看
♪ To realize... ♪
我今天发现
♪ I found out today ♪
我们做错了
♪ We're going wrong ♪
做错了
求你
♪ Please ♪
睁开双眼
♪ Open your eye ♪
我几天发现
♪ I found out today ♪
我们做错了
♪ We're going wrong ♪